Resume

I am a BA graduate,in the subject- Ancient Indian History,Archaeology and Culture.Apart from academics i have been actively taking part in extra xurricular activities,where i have been trained in various managerial and executive skills and I am willing to learn more. I assure to give my best if given an opportunity to prove myself. I seek to learn and gain hands on professional experience in the business world.

Personal details

Name Vinaya Keny

Email address vinayakeny3107@gmail.com

Phone number 9969183415

Address Bhandup, Mumbai 400078

Date of birth July 31, 2002

Gender Female



Education

Jun 2020 - May 2023 Bachelor Of Arts-Ancient Indian Culture, History and Archaeology

St. Xavier; s Autonomous College, Mumbai

Jun 2018 - Jun 2022 HSC

St.Xavier's College, Mumbai

HSC -82%

Jun 2017 - Jun 2018 SSC

Vidyadhiraja High School, Mumbai

School Topper-96%

Experience

Jun 2020 - Jan 2021 Voluntary work- Xavier's s Social Involvement Programme (SIP)

With an NGO-Mahek Foundation, Mumbai

Handled managerial tasks by working with social entrepreneurships.Learnt management of events, selection and elimination , managing data, communicating with large group of people and co-ordinating with other team members, etc

Dec 2022 - Present Teacher

Nrityanjali Institute of Performing Arts, Education, Personality Development, Social

& Management Services, Mumbai

As a part of this socio-cultural organization, where i am a part of the performing arts departments, i also assist in conducting inter school competitions , result

calculations, etc.

Dec 2018 Event Management

Kala Ghoda Arts Festival, Mumbai

Co-ordinated as a team member of the event management team with the Dance

department of the Kala Ghoda Arts Festival, Mumbai in 2019

Extra Curricular Engagement

■ Trained in Two classical dances -Kathak And Bharatnatyam, qualified university examinations of both.Performed at proffesional stages -Kala Ghoda Arts Festival, Mumbai, National Centre of Performing Arts, etc.